Aaron Booth 9422 Abney Ct Charlotte, NC 28227 Telephone- 704-962-9817 ABooth9422@gmail.com

ABootn9422@gmail.com
Abooth9422.github.io

I am a young father with striving ambition to do a great job. I am always looking for a challenge and a new atmosphere to sharpen my skills. Currently I'm looking for stability and a consistent scheduled job to meet my family needs. I work well with others and I am well spoken with customers and associates. I have worked retail for over 13 years and am very experienced and very technologically aware. I have experience using Microsoft Word, Excel, and Access through basic college courses. I am very efficient at data entry typing on average 65-70 WAM.

With my kids growing older I decided to pursue my dream and go back to school for Web Development. I have completed the UNCC web development bootcamp and am very passionate about being a designer. I specialize in front-end development making single page applications that are user friendly and mobile responsive. Although front-end development is my specialty, I love to do any type of development. To me web-design is something I truly enjoy and am very passionate about delivering a finished product on all of my school projects and endeavors.

Education:

Vance High School Charlotte, NC

Graduated: Class of 2007

Central Piedmont Community College 2007-2008

Charlotte, NC

Completed: 1 year towards an associate degree in Liberal Arts

UNCC Charlotte Web Development Bootcamp

April 2019-October 2019

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React.js,

Node.js, C#, .Net, Database Theory, Bookshelf.js, MongoDB,

MySQL, Command Line, and Git

Work Experience:

Netsafe Solutions Technical Support Specialist April 2019 to present

- -Managing a variety of company networks
- -Providing IT support on call to companies we support
- -Setting up company networks
- -Setting up company domains
- -Installing firewalls

- -System restore
- -Managing / setup devices on company network
- -Providing IT security from company's user-base
- -Consulting with companies and making recommendations on hardware to purchase that needs upgrades.
- -On-site support and installation

Petsmart Assistant Store Leader July 2017 to present

- -Daily Store operations
- -Managing over 40 employees
- -Payroll
- -Scheduling
- -Keeping Safety Standards
- -Hiring
- -Terminating employees
- -Delivering Corrective Action
- -Selling Services
- -Delivering Sales Goals
- -Holding team accountable to sales goals
- -Inventory Management
- -Shipping/Receiving

Party City General Manager May 2013 to July 2017

- -Maintaining structure of the store
- -Maintaining store operations
- -Evaluating employee's strengths and weaknesses
- -Hiring
- -Driving Sales
- -Planograms
- -Receiving
- -Store Maintenance inquiries
- -Cash handling procedure
- -Making sure store is always stocked and cleaned.
- -Ordering stock based on store needs and sales.
- -Creating a work friendly environment
- -Payroll
- -Safety committee

Party City. Assistant Manager Stores: 69, 70, 72 present #69. October 2011-May 2013.

- -Maintaining structure of the store
- -Daily operations of store
- -Cash handling procedures
- -Inventories
- -Holding associates accountable
- -Making sure store is crisp and pristine
- -Highly skilled in merchandising
- -Making enticing visuals for customers to view
- -Planograms & Resets

- -Receiving
- -Ownership of seasonal section
- -Adapting to any situation that may arise
- -Highly skilled in customer service.

Big Lots. Front End Supervisor. October 2009 - 2011

- -Maintaining and organizing the front end of the store.
- -Providing good customer service in all situations.
- -Returns, exchanges, refunds.
- -Preparing all defective merchandise for shipment.
- -Assisting manager in preparing bank deposits.
- -Answering the phone for customer inquiries.
- -Managing cashiers to ensure tasks are met.
- -Lead cashier, manager's assistant.

Circuit City. Product Flow. May 2008 - March 2009 (Out of Business)

- Unloading Trucks
- Stocking Shelves
- Merchandising all product
- Following Planograms
- Inventory
- Daily Media Maintenance
- Loading all TV's and Furniture
- Customer Assistance
- Merchandise Salesman (Video games, DVD's, CD's)
- Operating Stock picker

Bi-Lo. Bagger / Cashier. June 2005- May 2008

- Bagging all groceries for customers
- Providing good customer service
- Maintaining cleanliness and organizing front end
- Unloading Trucks
- Stocking Shelves
- Cashing out customers
- U-Scan

References:

Available upon request.